=== GRACE PERIOD ===
1st of June and 1st of December. At any time the grace period any time after the policy and will be entitled to all benefits and subject to commencement of risk or the date of revival of the gro@iciciprulife.com or 1800-2660. otherwise, you have an option to review the in treatment of such illness, is highly likely to during the instalment payment phase, the acquires a surrender value then the policy shall all liabilities as per the terms and conditions of the policy or the date of the rider to
---END---

=== FREE LOOK ===
You are not satisfied with Our resolution, extinguished. regarded as Terminally Ill only if that Life extinguished. 12. Modal loadings: Loadings for various modes of intimation of the death with the Company the 4) A policy of life insurance may be called in will be sourced from www.bloomberg.com. You may get in touch with Our designated 2. Free look period: On receipt of the policy A co s n s d u i r t e io d n is w h d i i c a h g , n os in e d th a e s s o u p f i f n e i r o in n g o fr f om
---END---

=== SURRENDER ===
option. For Limited Pay: Unexpired Risk Premium Value= 25% X [Number of months for which premiums are A. Paid-up Death Benefit paid / (Premium Payment Term X 12)] X [1 (Policy Month of surrender 1) / (Policy Term X 12)] X Total Premiums Paid. In the event of earlier death or terminal illness of the Life Assured during the policy term, the Paid-Up Death Benefit will be payable. For Regular Pay: Unexpired Risk Premium Value = 0 Paid-Up Death Benefit is higher of: The SSV factors shall be reviewed
---END---

=== DEATH BENEFIT ===
option. For Limited Pay: Unexpired Risk Premium Value= 25% X [Number of months for which premiums are A. Paid-up Death Benefit paid / (Premium Payment Term X 12)] X [1 (Policy Month of surrender 1) / (Policy Term X 12)] X Total Premiums Paid. In the event of earlier death or terminal illness of the Life Assured during the policy term, the Paid-Up Death Benefit will be payable. For Regular Pay: Unexpired Risk Premium Value = 0 Paid-Up Death Benefit is higher of: The SSV factors shall be reviewed
---END---

=== EXCLUSION ===
period means a consecutive period of 180 revival period, from time to time: In accordance to the Section 41 of the covered conditions fall within the exclusions materials or accident arising from such nature. The Policyholder will be required to pay goods and payment, Raheja Tipco Plaza, Rani Sati Marg, days commencing from the date of diagnosis of one the Insurance Act, 1938 as amended from time to Minor Condition to the date of diagnosis of a mentioned below.These exclusions apply in addition
---END---

=== TAX ===
Insurance Act, 1938 as the policy or the date of the rider to the policy, ground of fraud, the premiums collected on the Unit 901A & 901B, 9th Floor, Prism Towers, fax/paper: should neither be the insured person(s) himself from time to time. Please consult your tax amended from time to time: In accordance to the whichever is later. 2) A policy of life insurance policy till the date of repudiation shall be paid to Mindspace Link Road, Goregaon West, Post payment of such surrender value (if any),
---END---

=== CLAIM ===
lump sum at the time of acceptance of the claim. When to choose? You can opt for this facility at the inception of the policy or your claimant can opt it at the time of registration of claim. No additional premium is payable for this option. At any time during the instalment payment phase, the claimant can choose to terminate the instalment payment in exchange for a lump-sum, in which case, the lump-sum payable shall be equal to the discounted value of all the future instalments due. How is the
---END---

=== NOMINEE ===
may contact Our advisor or call Our customer Email ID: complaints@irdai.gov.in ssal.html for more details. nominee or beneficiary shall be entitled to an admitted. This feature is available to the Life amount shall be a level amount and once only be adjusted on the due date of the premium. Any person making default in complying with the mis-statement of or suppression of a material service representative (between 10.00 a.m. to amount which is higher of 80% of the total Assured underwritten as a
---END---

=== PREMIUM PAYMENT ===
option. For Limited Pay: Unexpired Risk Premium Value= 25% X [Number of months for which premiums are A. Paid-up Death Benefit paid / (Premium Payment Term X 12)] X [1 (Policy Month of surrender 1) / (Policy Term X 12)] X Total Premiums Paid. In the event of earlier death or terminal illness of the Life Assured during the policy term, the Paid-Up Death Benefit will be payable. For Regular Pay: Unexpired Risk Premium Value = 0 Paid-Up Death Benefit is higher of: The SSV factors shall be reviewed
---END---

=== MATURITY BENEFIT ===
premium value will be payable: under the policy will stand extinguished. Limited Pay In the event of death of the Life Assured or where the Life Assured is diagnosed with Terminal Illness on If one full years premium is not paid, Unexpired risk premium value = 0 the Date of Maturity for a Paid-up policy: With Return of Premium option: only the PaidUp Maturity Benefit (if applicable) is payable and the If one full years premium has been paid, then the Unexpired risk premium value = 25% X [Number
---END---

